{"test_questions": [[{"question": "1. I\n2. immediately\n3. salary\n\n4. my\n5. want", "opta": "43152", "optb": "15432", "optc": "25143", "optd": "42351", "opte": "45132", "ans": "B", "explanation": "\"I want my salary immediately.\""}, {"question": "1. do\n2. today\n3. you\n\n4. must\n5. it", "opta": "34152", "optb": "25413", "optc": "12543", "optd": "51324", "opte": "45213", "ans": "A", "explanation": "\"You must do it today.\""}, {"question": "1. left\n2. the\n3. house\n\n4. he\n5. suddenly", "opta": "12435", "optb": "21354", "optc": "45123", "optd": "52341", "opte": "24135", "ans": "C", "explanation": "\"He suddenly left the house.\""}, {"question": "1. medicine\n2. a\n3. Neeta\n\n4. given\n5. was", "opta": "51423", "optb": "25431", "optc": "15423", "optd": "42531", "opte": "35421", "ans": "E", "explanation": "\"Neeta was given a medicine.\""}, {"question": "1. of\n2. we\n3. heard\n\n4. him\n5. had", "opta": "42351", "optb": "52341", "optc": "25341", "optd": "25431", "opte": "25314", "ans": "E", "explanation": "\"We had heard of him.\""}, {"question": "1. at\n2. it\n3. take\n\n4. once\n5. away", "opta": "23514", "optb": "14352", "optc": "32514", "optd": "53214", "opte": "42315", "ans": "C", "explanation": "\"Take it away at once.\""}, {"question": "1. him\n2. the\n3. to\n\n4. charge\n5. handover", "opta": "42531", "optb": "51342", "optc": "41352", "optd": "45231", "opte": "52431", "ans": "E", "explanation": "\"Handover the charge to him.\""}, {"question": "1. seen\n2. going\n3. you\n\n4. him\n5. have", "opta": "35214", "optb": "35142", "optc": "32514", "optd": "35124", "opte": "53124", "ans": "B", "explanation": "\"You have seen him going.\""}, {"question": "1. bag?\n2. you\n3. seen\n\n4. have\n5. my", "opta": "51432", "optb": "43512", "optc": "42351", "optd": "42153", "opte": "21435", "ans": "C", "explanation": "\"Have you seen my bag?\""}, {"question": "1. killed\n2. a\n3. Jaswant\n\n4. bear\n5. wild", "opta": "31254", "optb": "53124", "optc": "23145", "optd": "43125", "opte": "15234", "ans": "A", "explanation": "\"Jaswant killed a wild bear.\""}, {"question": "1. was\n2. and\n3. Suresh\n\n4. kind\n5. loving", "opta": "31425", "optb": "54213", "optc": "34251", "optd": "15243", "opte": "12345", "ans": "A", "explanation": "\"Suresh was kind and loving.\""}, {"question": "1. tea\n2. have\n3. that\n\n4. some\n5. before", "opta": "43251", "optb": "24315", "optc": "24153", "optd": "52431", "opte": "41325", "ans": "C", "explanation": "\"Have some tea before that.\""}, {"question": "1. not\n2. hotel\n3. comfortable\n\n4. was\n5. the", "opta": "34521", "optb": "53412", "optc": "34152", "optd": "41352", "opte": "52413", "ans": "E", "explanation": "\"The hotel was not comfortable.\""}, {"question": "1. I\n2. help\n3. not\n\n4. you\n5. did", "opta": "24351", "optb": "15324", "optc": "45231", "optd": "43152", "opte": "52431", "ans": "B", "explanation": "\"I did not help you.\""}, {"question": "1. not\n2. Hari\n3. away\n\n4. run\n5. did", "opta": "13542", "optb": "35412", "optc": "52431", "optd": "25143", "opte": "21345", "ans": "D", "explanation": "\"Hari did not run away.\""}]]}